http://www.nanigans.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Last updated: May 24, 2018
Introduction
At Nanigans, Inc. (“Nanigans”, “the Company”, “us”), we take privacy issues seriously. The following is an outline of the ways in which we collect and use the personal information you provide on our web site www.nanigans.com and through the Nanigans Ad Automation Software (our “Services”). It also describes the choices available to you and the rights that you have regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.
If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, then please contact us using the contact details provided at the bottom of this Policy.
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
What Does Nanigans Do?
Nanigans is a software company headquartered in Boston with offices in New York, San Francisco, London, and Singapore. The world’s most successful in-house marketing teams deliver relevant advertising to their ideal customers through Nanigans’ best-in-class software solution. Companies from across the globe rely on Nanigans’ software and consultative customer service to help them grow incremental revenue from their marketing efforts on Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, and online display networks.
QUICK LINKS
We recommend that you read this privacy policy in full to ensure you are fully informed.
However, to make it easier for you to review those parts of this privacy policy which apply to you, we have divided up the document into the following sections:
Introduction
What Does Nanigans Do?
Information Collection and Use
Analytics/Log Files
Referral
Information Sharing
Legal Disclaimer
Your Data Protection Rights
Cookies, Web Beacons, and Tracking
Cookies on our properties
Cookies used in advertising
3rd party tracking
Web Opt-Out (Nanigans.com)
Mobile Opt-Out
Android users
iOS users
Email Opt-out
Information Related to Data Collected through Nanigans Ad Automation Software
Access and choice
LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION (EEA VISITORS ONLY)
International data transfers
Data retention and security
Additional Information
Links to 3rd party sites
Blog
Testimonials
Social media widgets
Changes to this policy
Contacting us
Information Collection and Use
We don’t collect data that people commonly understand to be personal, such as names, addresses, etc. However the concept of “personal data” under GDPR is a broad one.
If you are a Nanigans customer, Nanigans’ tracking solutions may gather first-party data on individuals. In the case of website pixels, a combination of unique user IDs, cookies, and IP addresses are used for attribution purposes. In situations where the Nanigans SDK is in place for mobile app integrations, unique user IDs and device / advertising IDs (IDFA, GDFA, Android ID) are collected for attribution purposes. Additionally, device specific user-agent and IP address data is carried by all network requests and collected along with the data listed above. The information that we do receive is generated from ‘clicks’ and/or impressions on our ads and enables us to best provide our customers with effective targeting and feedback.
Customer accounts with Nanigans are only available to advertisers. For these accounts, we hold user submitted information such as username and password in order to authenticate users and to contact users with relevant information having to do with their Nanigans accounts.
If you visit our website or receive our email newsletter, we may collect your contact information such as name, email address, mailing address, and phone number. We may use this information for internal purposes to send you a requested product, respond to your service requests, questions or concerns, administer your account, send you newsletters or catalogues in accordance with your marketing and communication preferences, and/or to improve our web site and marketing efforts.
Analytics/Log Files
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes information that may be regarded as personal information in certain countries, such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), search terms, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.
We use this information, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.
Referral
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a performance marketer about our software, we will ask you for that person’s name and email address. We will automatically send that person a one-time email inviting him/her to visit the website. Nanigans stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Please, make sure that you only provide us with these contact details when you have that person’s permission to do so.
Information Sharing
We will only share your personal information with third parties in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may disclose your personal information to the following categories of recipients:
Third-party providers: We may share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. These services may include sending marketing communications or providing cloud computing infrastructure for example.
To our group companies who provide data processing services to us, or who otherwise process personal information for purposes that are described in this Privacy Policy or given to you when we collect your personal information. A list of our current group companies is available here.
To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.
Legal Disclaimer
We may also disclose your personal information:
in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements or as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
if Nanigans is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or use of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
Your Data Protection Rights
Nanigans acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. Upon request Nanigans will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If customers wish to change their personal information (i.e. contact info, username, password) they should feel free to contact us at info@nanigans.com.
If you are a customer that no longer desires our service, you may deactivate your account by emailing our Customer Support at info@nanigans.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within 30 days.
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you have the following data protection rights:
If you wish to correct or update your personal information, you can do so at any time by contacting us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting us” heading below.
If you wish to access or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by clicking on the following links: http://www.nanigans.com/request-token-info ; http://www.nanigans.com/forget-me
In addition, you can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting us” heading below.
Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.
We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.
Cookies, Web Beacons, and Tracking
Nanigans and our partners use cookies, web beacons, and similar tracking technologies on our websites and mobile applications as well as those of our advertisers. Cookies are small files that are placed on your browser or device by the website or app you are using or ad you have viewed. Some cookies contain personal information, such as an identifier that can be used to connect the actions of an individual visitor on a website, while others contain anonymous information used in site operations.
There are two types of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Simply exiting your browser will remove all session cookies. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory.
We employ a software technology called Web Beacons (a.k.a. clear gifs) along with cookies. Web beacons are tiny graphics or scripts embedded in web pages, which are used to track information about the behavior of individual visitors, such as which products they browse over time. Web beacons cannot generally be disabled, but they rely on cookies to identify visitors.
Cookies on our properties
On the nanigans.com website and within our advertising platform, we use cookies to provide you with a better, faster or safer experience. Cookies are used to understand, improve, and research products and services. For example, cookies may be used on our website to understand how you are using social plugins in order to improve them, and in our platform to track usage and performance of individual features. They may also be used to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We partner with other companies in these efforts, and may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.
We use session cookies for functions such as server load balancing and denial-of-service attack protection, and persistent cookies for login, analytics, and marketing. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site may be limited. Our platform requires an authorized login and cannot operate without cookies.
Cookies used in advertising
Advertisers use our platform to reach prospective customers across a variety of web and social properties. Our platform utilizes cookies and beacons placed in their sites and apps to help them advertise more effectively. It places ‘analytical’ and ‘operational’ persistent cookies. Analytical cookies allow us to identify visitors and measure how they interact with our advertisers’ sites and advertisements. This helps us to improve the effectiveness of advertising by delivering personalized ads to the visitors who find them most relevant. Operational cookies contain no personal information and are support operations of the advertising system such as segment management and pixel forwarding. Our platform also facilitates the insertion of web beacons from publishers, who may also place cookies for advertising purposes.
As an example of the use of cookies and tracking in advertising, a you may be shown an ad placed by the Nanigans platform as you browse websites, use mobile apps, or interact on social networks. A click or tap on the ad will take you to our advertiser’s site or app. At that point, a Nanigans beacon would place a cookie on your browser and our platform would analyze your usage of the site or app. If you show interest in certain products, the platform can tune future advertisements to be more relevant to you based on that information. If you show little interest, the platform can learn that the ad it showed you was irrelevant or poorly placed, and avoid showing it to others in the future.
3rd party tracking
The use of cookies and clear gifs by our technology partners and service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. Our technology partners and service providers use trackers to optimize your experience on our site and help them better manage content on our site.
Web Opt-Out (Nanigans.com)
If you choose not to receive the benefits of cookies, you may ‘opt-out‘ by clicking the following link: Opt-Out
Please be aware that because cookies are browser specific, if you use more than one browser on your computer, you will need to repeat the opt-out process on the other browser(s) in order to opt-out completely. Please note that you will need to opt out of the Nanigans’ cookie again if you buy a new computer, upgrade or change the browser on your existing computer, or delete the Nanigans opt-out cookie. If you wish to opt back in, you may do so by deleting the Nanigans opt-out cookie from your browser.
Mobile Opt-Out
Android users
You may opt-out of Nanigans Mobile Tracking by downloading and installing our Do Not Track Application, located here: http://www.nanigans.com/AndroidDoNotTrack.apk
iOS users
For iOS 7 and 8 users
From your iOS home screen, go to Settings -> Privacy -> Advertising
On the Advertising screen, turn “Limit Ad Tracking” on
Please note that this is a global setting and will disable ad tracking on the device level, not just for Nanigans
For iOS 6 Users
From your iOS home screen, go to Settings -> General -> About -> Advertising
On the Advertising screen, turn “Limit Ad Tracking” on
Please note that this is a global setting and will disable ad tracking on the device level, not just for Nanigans
Email Opt-out
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or by e-mailing us at myinfo@nanigans.com with “My Info” in the subject line of the e-mail or by contacting us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting Us” heading below. We will send you an e-mail to confirm your request. After we receive confirmation from you, we will correct or remove your information from all active databases.
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
Information Related to Data Collected through Nanigans Ad Automation Software
Access and choice
Individuals who seek access, or who seek to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data that is collected through Nanigans’ Services, should contact Nanigans via the above links. If any of our customers request Nanigans remove data that the customer controls upon demand of a 3rd party, we will respond to their request within 30 days. Nanigans may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our services. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our customers.
LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION (EEA VISITORS ONLY)
If you are a member from the European Economic Area, our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.
However, we will normally collect personal information from you only where we have your consent to do so, where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you.
If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information).
Similarly, if we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.
If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us using the contact details provided under the “Contacting us” heading below.
International data transfers
Your personal information may be transferred to, and processed in, countries other than the country in which you are resident. These countries may have data protection laws that are different to the laws of your country.
However, we have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your personal information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy. These include implementing the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses for transfers of personal information between our group companies, which require all group companies to protect personal information they process from the EEA in accordance with European Union data protection law.
Our Standard Contractual Clauses can be provided on request. We have implemented similar appropriate safeguards with our third party service providers and partners and further details can be provided upon request.
Data retention and security
Nanigans will retain both the information we collect directly and personal data we process through our customers for as long as needed to provide services to our customers. We will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
When we have no longer have legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymise it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.
We take the security of information that we collect very seriously and therefore implement appropriate technical and organizational measures in order to protect it. When you log into our Ad Automation Software, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at info@nanigans.com.
Additional Information
Links to 3rd party sites
Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Nanigans. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.
Blog
Our Web site offers a publicly accessible blog. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog, contact us at info@nanigans.com.
Testimonials
We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at info@nanigans.com.
Social Media widgets
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and other Widgets, such as the Sharaholic. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Changes to this policy
We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site depending on the significance of the changes that we make prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Contacting us
Any questions, complaints or general comments should be directed to info@nanigans.com.
You may also reach us at:
(888) 507-4456
100 Summer Street, 31st Floor
Boston, MA 02110
For EEA Residents:
London
c/o WeWork, 1 Fore Street
London, EC2Y 5EJ.
For the purposes of EU data protection legislation, Nanigans, Inc. is the controller of your personal information.
By continuing to browse this website, you accept Nanigans’ use of cookies for marketing, analytics, and other purposes. Click here to learn more or change your cookie settings.
Accept
Privacy Overview
Strictly Necessary Cookies
3rd Party Cookies
Powered by GDPR plugin
Privacy Overview
Nanigans uses cookies for marketing, analytics, and other purposes. Please click here to view our full privacy policy.
You can adjust all of your cookie settings by navigating the tabs in this window.
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Strictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.
disable
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.
3rd Party Cookies
This website uses Google Analytics to collect anonymous information such as the number of visitors to the site, and the most popular pages.
Keeping this cookie enabled helps us to improve our website.
disable
Please enable Strictly Necessary Cookies first so that we can save your preferences!
Enable All
Save Changes
